If you have a common table expression or subquery that takes a really long time to run,
إذا كان لدينا تعبير جدولي شهير أو استعلام فرعي يستغرق وقتًا طويلًا ليعمل،
you might want to run it as a completely separate query and
يحتمل أن ترغب في تشغيله كاستعلام منفصل تمامًا
then write it back into the database as it's own table.
ومن ثم إعادة كتابته في قاعدة البيانات كالجدول الخاص به.
Then, you can simply query the new table as you would any other,
ثم، يمكنكم ببساطة الاستعلام عن الجدول الجديد حيث ترغبون،
to finish the things you're trying to calculate.
أن ينهي أي أحد آخر الأشياء التي حاولت حسابها.
The big benefit to this approach is that you can improve the speed at which you explore.
إن الفائدة الكبيرة لهذه المحاولة هي أنكم باستطاعتكم تحسين السرعة التي اكتشفتموها.
Let's say you've got a subquery that takes an hour to write,
لنقل أنكم لديكم استعلام فرعي يستغرق ساعة ليُكتب،
and then you've got an outer query that's pretty fast.
ومن ثم لديكم استعلام خارجي سريع جدًا.
If you run both of them every time you want to make a small tweak to the outer query,
إذا قمتم بتشغيل كليهما في كل مرة ترغبون في إجراء تغيير للاستعلام الخارجي،
you're going to get really frustrated.
ستصابون بالإحباط.
Instead, you can run that inner query once and write it to a table,
وبدلًا من هذا، فإنك تستطيع تشغيل الاستعلام الداخلي مرة ثم تكتبه في جدول،
then iterating on the outer query will be quick and easy.
ومن ثم تكرره في الاستعلام الخارجي مما سيكون سريعًا وسهلًا.
We'll dig into performance in more depth in later lessons.
سنتعمق في الأداء أكثر في الدروس اللاحقة.
For now, we'll focus on writing your subqueries and
والآن، سنركز على كتابة الاستعلامات الفرعية
common table expressions into the database as new tables.
والتعبيرات المشتركة للجدول في قاعدة البيانات كالجداول الجديدة.